{
    "data": [
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What is ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter is a DynamiCrafter that works natively with ComfyUI's nodes, optimizations, ControlNet, and more."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What is required to get ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter installed?",
            "answer": "Go to your `custom_nodes` directory in ComfyUI, and install by `git clone https://github.com/ExponentialML/ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter.git`."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "Where can the last stable branch can be found?",
            "answer": "[here](https://github.com/ExponentialML/ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter/tree/43ae6bebccb141c6d85b5075f4fed57a5ddea3c1)"
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What models are used with ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "A VAE, The CLIP model used with Stable Diffusion 2.1, and the Open CLIP Vision Model."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "Where are the DynamiCrafter models placed?",
            "answer": "DynamiCrafter models are placed inside `ComfyUI_Path/models/dynamicrafter_models`."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What is the use of `use_interpolation` in ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "Use the interpolation mode with the interpolation model variant. You can interpolate any two frames (images), or predict the rest using one input."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What is the range of values for `fps` in ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "If you're using a 256 based model, the highest plausible value is **4**."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What is the maximum value for `frames` in ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "The max is **16**."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "Can ControlNet be used with ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "Yes, ControlNet can be used with ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter by applying it to the Spatial (image) portion to guide video generations in various ways."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "Can you use your own latents with ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "Yes, as long as you use the same frame length (as your batch size) and same height and width as your image inputs, you can use your own latents."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter",
            "question": "What are the future plans for ComfyUI_Native_DynamiCrafter?",
            "answer": "Add advanced workflows, autoregressive nodes, and ensure attention optimizations are working properly."
        }
    ]
}